const QuestionArray=[
    {question:"Zwiebeln",answers:["Onion","Pencil","Apple","Kiwi"],correct:"Onion"},
    {question:"Kartoffeln",answers:["Week","Day","Potato","Onion"],correct:"Potato"},
    {question:"Heute",answers:["Tomorrow","Today","Yesterday","Morning"],correct:"Today"},
    {question:"Machen",answers:["Play","Go","Do","Kiwi"],correct:"Do"},
    {question:"Schon",answers:["Beatiful","Ugly","Handsome","Husband"],correct:"Beatiful"},
    {question:"Wasser",answers:["Onion","Water","Carrot","Banana"],correct:"Water"},
    {question:"Kurz",answers:["Short","Long","Big","Small"],correct:"Short"},
    {question:"Dunkel",answers:["Red","Blue","Dark","Yellow"],correct:"Dark"},
    {question:"Hoch",answers:["High","Smoke","Nuts","Thing"],correct:"High"},
    {question:"Handy",answers:["Phone","Call","Back","Forward"],correct:"Phone"},
    {question:"Rufen",answers:["Call","Phone","Back","Forward"],correct:"Call"}
    
]
export default QuestionArray